davidbach.com 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement and Policy

David Bach and FinishRich take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. To learn more about our other website policies, please read our Terms of Use.

What this Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers David Bach's and FinishRich's treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the finishrich.com website. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that David Bach and FinishRich do not own or control, or to people that David Bach and FinishRich do not employ or manage. 

Information Collection and Use

David Bach and FinishRich, Inc collect and maintain personally identifiable information that you provide us when you subscribe for Mr. Bach's free newsletter, when you complete a class registration form for Smart Women Finish Rich and Smart Couples Finish Rich classes, when you buy products at our Finish Rich store, and when you wish to hire Mr. Bach as a speaker. When you register with finishrich.com, we ask for your name, mailing address, zip code, telephone number and email address. When you buy a Finish Rich store product, we also ask for a credit card number. When you assert interest in hiring Mr. Bach as a speaker, we request specific information about your speaking event. Once you register with finishrich.com, you are not anonymous to us. David Bach and FinishRich use your personal information for three general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products, services and information that you have requested, to respond to your inquiries and to contact you about new products and services. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

David Bach and FinishRich will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. When you provide your contact information and indicate an interest in attending the Smart Women Finish Rich and Smart Couples Finish Rich classes, in order to respond to your interest, we will forward this information to Van Kampen Investments Inc., a financial institution with which we have a joint marketing arrangement, which will send the information to a local financial adviser who is trained to present the class. When you disclose your information, a financial adviser may contact you. Neither Van Kampen nor any financial adviser may use or disclose your contact information except for the purpose of inviting you to a class, or to the extent that you have an independent customer relationship with such party(ies). Accordingly, when you provide your contact information and indicate interest in attending a seminar, you are giving consent for us to forward your information via Van Kampen to a local financial adviser. We may also need to disclose your personal information as required or permitted by law i.e., to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process. 

Editing Account Information and Unsubscribing from the Newsletter

You have the ability to edit any personal information associated with your account on the Account Settings page. **When you are logged in** you can access this by clicking on 'Account' located on the upper right hand side of the page. On the Account Settings page, you may edit/add personal information or subscribe/unsubscribe from our free monthly newsletter.

Security

We permit access to our website and the personal information that you provide us only by our authorized employees with passwords in order to protect against the improper disclosure of you personal information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. To protect your personal information, we maintain online safeguards. We use CyberCash to process our transaction, as well as industry-standard security technologies, including SSL-encryption and the CyberCash-provided 3DES solution. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

David Bach and FinishRich may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions please use our contact form.
